Nikolay Motev

Quality Assurance Engineer

PROFILE

motivated Highly technology professional, launching a career as a software quality engineer. Quick learner with excellent knowledge retention. Highly organized with the ability to prioritize tasks efficiently. Hands-on experience in the testing of software systems supporting products and interfaces. Knowledge of standard industry QA methodologies and the Software Development Life Cycle (SDLC).

EDUCATION / CERTIFICATE

Skillo - Sofia

Quality Assurance Engineer Certficate for Software testing QA 2022

Software University - Sofia

Quality Assurance Engineer Certificate Programming Basics C#

Technical University of Gabrovo

Master`s degree

Textile Technique and Technology 2017/2019

Technical University of Gabrovo

Bachelor degree

Textile Technique and Technology 1997/2000

LANGUAGES

Bulgarian - Native English - Advanced knowledge



CONTACT

- + 359 8799 95978
- mmotev@yahoo.com
- https://www.linkedin.com/in/nikolaymotev-10657659/
- Pleven, Bulgaria

WORK EXPERIENCE

Small Bussines Sales: 2018 - ongoing

Niro Pro Trade Pleven, Bulgaria

Shift Engineer: 03/2013 - 06/2017

Telehouse Europe London, United Kingdom

Data Engineer: 09/2012 - 02/2013 ICobus Limited - London, United Kingdom

Data Cable Engineer: 05/2012 - 08/2012 NETCOM 92 – London, United Kingdom

SKILLS

- Database and SQL
- Git
- HTML
- Test Cases, Bugs
- Mobile Testing Software Testing Life Cycle • XML
- Regression testing
- Web services, Postman
- Types of Testing
- Testing Techniques
- CSS
- **JSON**